{
    "subject": "resource/A_Price_Above_Rubies",
    "predicate": "property/released",
    "object": "August 1999",
    "human_readable": "The movie 'A Price Above Rubies' was released in August 1999.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9854890704154968,
            "question": "Was 'A Price Above Rubies' a new release in August 1999?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9806357026100159,
            "question": "Is 'A Price Above Rubies' a film from the year 1999?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9774137735366821,
            "question": "Is the movie 'A Price Above Rubies' associated with the year 1999?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9262990951538086,
            "question": "When was the movie 'A Price Above Rubies' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9015042781829834,
            "question": "Which movie was released in August of 1999?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8856478929519653,
            "question": "Did 'A Price Above Rubies' come out in the late summer of 1999?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8470848202705383,
            "question": "What is the name of the movie released in August 1999?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.75794517993927,
            "question": "What month marked the release of the film 'A Price Above Rubies'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7433017492294312,
            "question": "What year did 'A Price Above Rubies' premiere?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6933131217956543,
            "question": "In what month was 'A Price Above Rubies' released?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The movie 'A Price Above Rubies' was released in August 1999.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7931_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year did 'A Price Above Rubies' premiere?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7931_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What month marked the release of the film 'A Price Above Rubies'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7931_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the movie released in August 1999?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7931_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7931_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7931_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7931_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7931_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7931_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7931_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7931_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7931_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7931_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7931_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe document states that the film was released in May 1999, not August 1999. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents contain information about the release date of the movie \"A Price Above Rubies\", which is Sunday, 16 May 1999. This supports the triple that the movie was released in May 1999, not August 1999."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided context does not mention the release date of the movie \"A Price Above Rubies.\" Therefore, we cannot confirm that it was released in August 1999 based on the given information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The release date of the movie \"A Price Above Rubies\" is stated as May 1999, not August 1999.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}